{
    "subject": "resource/1868_Thersites",
    "predicate": "property/discovered",
    "object": "1960-09-24",
    "human_readable": "Thersites was discovered on September 24, 1960.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8165727853775024,
            "question": "When was Thersites discovered?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7717075347900391,
            "question": "Who discovered Thersites?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7324554920196533,
            "question": "Where was Thersites discovered from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5573028922080994,
            "question": "Has Thersites been studied further since its initial discovery?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5041304230690002,
            "question": "How was Thersites named?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5002387166023254,
            "question": "What methods were used to discover Thersites?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.32082152366638184,
            "question": "What impact has the discovery of Thersites had on our understanding of the solar system?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22007648646831512,
            "question": "Is there any further information about Thersites' characteristics or orbit?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.16086675226688385,
            "question": "What type of celestial object is Thersites?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.12186115235090256,
            "question": "Are there any other asteroids with similar characteristics to Thersites?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Thersites was discovered on September 24, 1960.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4287_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of celestial object is Thersites?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4287_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there any further information about Thersites' characteristics or orbit?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4287_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What impact has the discovery of Thersites had on our understanding of the solar system?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4287_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4287_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4287_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4287_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4287_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4287_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4287_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4287_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4287_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4287_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4287_72.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents mention that an asteroid named Thersites (1868) was discovered on September 24, 1960. This information directly supports the triple statement."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that both Asteroid 1868 Thersites and 9817 Thersander were discovered on September 24, 1960. Therefore, the statement \"Thersites was discovered on September 24, 1960\" is supported by the provided context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}